欢迎喜欢的朋友加入familyguy百度贴吧共同讨论
或加FG粉丝交流 QQ群 165859780
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Family Guy 10x08
Cool Hand Peter
酷汉皮特
标题恶搞了《Cool Hand Luke》
一部描述监狱生活的电影
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: zurica wudixny 后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组
这么说 Cleveland 你已经彻底看穿了
So, Cleveland, you got to be pretty psyched
尤巴马总统 是吧
about President Ubama, huh?
什么
W-What?
呃 我是说 你记得许多人都是怎么说的 比如
Well, I mean, you remember how a lot of people said, like,
"哦 尤巴马不能胜任那件事"
"Oh, Ubama's not gonna be able to do it,"
可他还真的坚持下去了
but he's-he's hanging in there.
Peter 那是奥巴马
Peter, it's "Obama."
呃 你巴马 我巴马 咱巴马 谁在乎
Eh, You-bama, Me-bama, We-bama, who cares?
不过是个黑人穿了西装 让人有点另眼相看罢了
It's a black guy in a suit, let's just marvel at that.
Cleveland 真是太好了
Gosh, Cleveland, it sure is great
你回到了Clam酒吧 虽然只有短短一周
having you back at The Clam, even if it's just for a week.
(ringtone): ♪ My name is Cleveland Brown ♪
♪ And I am proud to be... ♪
哦 等等 是我的手机响了
Oh, hang on, that's my cell phone.
哇 Peter 你用这首歌做铃声
Aw, Peter, you're using the song!
谢谢你
Thank you.
呃 其实这曲子不咋地
Well, the numbers ain't so good,
所以我们得尽力把它派上用场——啥事 Lois
so we got to do everything we can-- Hello, Lois.
Peter 你又野到哪儿去了
Peter, where the hell are you?
你跟我说过会清理地下室里的那些箱子
You told me you were gonna clean out those boxes in the basement
把它们搬到阁楼上
and put them in the attic.
Lois 那些听着像附加作业啊
Lois, it just sounds like busy work.
busy work指学校为防止学生无所事事而布置的额外作业
就是附加作业
It is busy work.
我就是要让你远离街头混混 远离毒品
I'm trying to keep you off the streets and off drugs.
可我已经把糖果卖完了
I'm selling those candy bars!
喂 喂 喂 喂 你想买些糖果吗
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you want to buy some candy bars
这样我们有钱给自己的棒球队买新队服
so we can get some new uniforms for our baseball team?
你从哪儿弄来的那些糖果
Where'd you get those candy bars?
Peter 我需要你回家
Peter, I need you home.
你也答应过会修好车库里的那个架子
You also promised you'd fix that shelf in the garage.
啊 Lois 我听不清你说话
Oh, Lois, I'm losing you.
喂 喂
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
嗨 Lois
Oh, hey, Lois.
我现在是另一个人了
This is somebody else now.
肯定是串线了
There must've been a cross connection.
我叫Mike 我在别处
My name is Mike, and I'm somewhere else
正要打自己的电话
trying to make my own call.
好的 Mike
Fine, Mike.
请你转告Peter 他回家之后麻烦就大了
You tell Peter he's in trouble when he gets home.
你可以自己告诉他 因为Mike就是Peter
You can tell him yourself, because Mike is Peter!
哎呀妈呀
Oh, my God.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
装得挺像的嘛 Peter
That was very good, Peter.
我知道
I know!
我勒个去
Geez.
我最近的生活就是这样 各种杂七杂八的事
That's all my life is lately, just a bunch of chores.
我真是厌倦了Lois总叫我做这些傻逼事
I'm sick of Lois always making me do stupid stuff.
我懂你所说的 Peter
I know what you're saying, Peter.
Bonnie也总是叫我做
Bonnie's always making me do
那些无法完成的家务活
all these impossible household tasks.
BONNIE: Joe 你得确保
BONNIE: Joe, make sure you get
把地毯上的那些车胎印都清理干净
all the tire tracks out of the carpet.
试着接受这些胎印吧 Bonnie
Learn to live with it, Bonnie!
就是些印记罢了
There are tracks!
是个人就会留下印记
People make tracks!
唉 我也懂你说的
Boy, I hear you, too.
得花很多功夫才能
It's a lot of work just to keep
保持我的单身汉冰箱足够空敞
my single guy fridge sufficiently depressing.
我看看啊
Let's see.
前女友的Yoplait酸奶
Ex-girlfriend's Yoplait.
一个法国牌子的酸奶
两年前的沙士饮料
Root beer from two Julys ago.
找到了 过期的牛奶
Here we go, expired milk.
哎哟喂 Jenny 看看你那会儿多小啊
Oh, my God, Jenny, look how young you look.
你把萌妹子在地窖里关了十几年吗 Giggity
我和你们感同身受啊
I sympathize with y'all.
Donna让我在XM Radio上一天听19个小时的Gayle King
Donna makes me listen to Gayle King on XM Radio 19 hours a day.
Gayle King是自由编辑 奥普拉的好友 XM Radio是一个卫星广播频道
我都想要自杀了
I tried to kill myself by
吞了一把指甲刀 可还是没死成
swallowing a nail clipper, but I passed it.
00:0